Previously on
The Big Bang Theory:
Guess who I found at LAX.
My baby sister Priya.
It's really nice
to see you again, Leonard.
Yeah, it's good
to see you, too.
Here you go.
(Howard:)Thanks.
You slept with
my sister?!
(Howard:)Yeah.
This is a terrible
betrayal of my trust!
Would it help
if I told you
that I offered
her my heart,
and she kinda
stomped on it?!
How hard did she stomp?
Very hard.
Okay, I'm good.
(Howard:)What's so funny?
(Bernadette:)Nothing. Just thinking
(Bernadette:)about the noises people
make during sex.
(Howard:)I do sometimes get a bit
carried away, don't I?
(Bernadette:)It's cute.
(Bernadette:)You sound a little
like a drunken monkey.
(Bernadette:)Ooh-ooh-ooh-ooh!
(Howard:)You know it's meant
as a compliment.